<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>/home/nkallergis/</title>
    <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on /home/nkallergis/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:03:54 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nkallergis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20201106</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/posts/20201106/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:03:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/posts/20201106/</guid>
      <description>Initial commit :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/about</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 14:23:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/about/</guid>
      <description>Nikos Kallergis  Unified Skillset primarily focused on networking
Worked as  Network Automation Engineer Network Field Engineer Network Presales Engineer Network Design Engineer  Experienced in  Routing Switching Security Wireless IP Telephony  Currently working on  Automation/Orchestration Telemetry &amp;amp; Observability Cloud &amp;amp; Network Virtualization NetDevOps  Tools of choice  VSCode Wireshark Whiteboard Ansible Python Nornir Nautobot NAPALM  Contact details LinkedIn * Mail * Phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/education</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/education/</guid>
      <description>  Formal education Technological Educational Institute of Athens: Dpt of Informatics
Seminars, webinars and courses &amp;ldquo;Building network automation solutions&amp;rdquo; by ipSpace.net
Certifications  AZ-300 Microsoft Azure Architect Technologies CCSA Check Point Certified Security Administrator CCSE Check Point Certified Security Expert CCNA Cisco Certified Network Associate - Routing and Switching CCIE Cisco Certified Internetwork Expert - R&amp;amp;S (written exam only) CCP-N Citrix Certified Professional - Networking CC-SDWAN Citrix NetScaler SD-WAN Certified  Languages  Greek (native) English (full proficiency) French (limited proficiency) Spanish (limited proficiency)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/experience</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/experience/</guid>
      <description>Senior Consultant at Network to Code November 2021 - present
For the past couple of years, I’ve been working as a Network Automation Engineer, helping customers transform their teams and network operations. A blend of networking, automation/orchestration, telemetry, and Python/Django development.
 Professional services architect at UniSystems November 2019 - November 2021
As a result of the below and in conjunction with the experience I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered from all my previous positions, my title was changed to &amp;ldquo;Architect&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/projects</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/bio/projects/</guid>
      <description>MacStadium Telemetry June 2023 - September 2023
Migrate from a commercial monitoring solution to an open-source telemetry and alerting stack (Nautobot, Telegraf, Prometheus, Grafana, AlertManager).
 Bank Central Asia Network Automation January 2023 - May 2023
Joined the Network Automation team of BCA and helped design their automation strategy. As part of that, managed to push Nautobot to production, deliver a catalog of services to business stakeholders, and set the basis for automated data center deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20201002</title>
      <link>https://nkallergis.github.io/posts/20201002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 16:31:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkallergis.github.io/posts/20201002/</guid>
      <description>Pre-commit</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
